Take a look at IC I
Lord, if seen from the trading point of view,
how does it look?
As per this current trading, I am also
not seeing any formation in it. Kanchan ji, if
I talk, then from the entire first month till now,
except for two spots, one candle went to
almost 4 and after that it again fell to 4 on
its second or third day, so I mean to say,
apart from these two moves, there is no
momentum going on in it, no bike is visible,
low volume is visible, according to me, there is still no
place for trading in it,
yes, if it comes to 15202 in correction, then
you should take a position there, from
there
you will get a trading bet for trading, when it bounces back from there,
then you can go to 1650 and 1700, but keep in mind that
you will not get anything by buying here,
I feel that correction is on the cards
when so many pin bars are being formed, a
pin bar is being formed on the top, so according to me,
as soon as this pin bar  The loses of the bars will be broken, the
level of 1620 and 1610 will be broken, I think there will be an
immediate correction till 1550 and 1450, yes yes, it
is fine.